- Is this on? - That's fine.
玲克必并了吗 ? 天了
l can break through walls, I just can't...
多厚的炉壁我都能撞破 我各不能…
- That's fine. - [can't get this on.
可以了 这玩意我各搞不定
So, Mr. Incredible... Do you have a secret identity?
超能先生
Every superhero has a secret identity. I don't know a single one who doesn''t.
每个超级英雄都有秘密身份
Who wants the pressure of being super all the time?
当超级英雄的压力呀?
Of course I have a secret identity.
我当然有秘密身份唾
Can you see me in this at the supermarket? Come on.
(弹力女超人 )
Who'd want to go shopping as Elastigirl, know what I mean?
当弹力女超人该怎广血拼呀? 你盯吗 ?
Superladies, they're always trying to tell you their secret identity.
女超人都喜霓 向我透露秘密身份
Think it'll strengthen the relationship or something.
(酷冰使)
Il said, "Girl, 1 don't want to know about your mild-mannered alter ego."
我说 : 拜斌 我才不想知道你温柔的一面
I mean, you tell me you're a super-mega-ultra-lightning-babe,
你超级露震动爆的一面
that's all right with me. I'm good. I'm good.
我反而比较喜驳 我最爱了，我超爱的
No matter how many times you save the world,
不管你抒救世界多少避
it always manages to get back in jeopardy again.
世界还是会再度陷入危机
Sometimes I just want it to stay saved, you know?
有时候我真希望它能真的安全
For a little bit. feel like the maid. "] just cleaned up this mess.
只有一下子也好 我好像清党女工，才打抬乾泽
Can we keep it clean for ten minutes?"
拜旗能不能保持十分甸 列那广快就弄器
- [could get to that point. - "Please?"
我懂你的意思 拜旗…
Sometimes I think I'd just like the simple life, you know?
有了时候我只想单纯地通日子
Relax a little and raise a family.
好好享受家庭生活
Settle down? Are you kidding? I'm at the top of my game!
定下来?别开玩笑了 我现在这广成功
I'm up there with the big dogs! Girls, come on.
我是这行数一数二的高手 拜斌
Leave the saving of the world to the men? I don't think so.
要我等著让男人摊救世界 ? 我才不要呢 !
I don't think so.
想都列想
We interrupt for an important bulletin.
这是一则最新消息
A deadly high-speed pursuit between police and armed gunmen is underway,
整方和持检歹徒 正在本巴四大道
traveling northbound on San Pablo Ave.
展开一场蓝险的未车追逐
Mr. Incredible.
超能先生
- What is it, ma'am? - My cat, Squeaker, won't come down.
什么事，女士 ? 我的猫噶噶不此下来
Certainly. l suggest you stand clear. There could be trouble.
没问题，不明请你让并 可能会有危险
No, he's quite tame.
不会啦，拖很乖的
Let go now.
快下来
Thank you, Mr. Incredible. You've done it again.
谢谢你，超能先生 你又帮了大忙
- You're the best. - No, I'm just here to help.
你最棒 我很乐意帮忙
Attention all units. We have a tour bus robbery...
请注意 发生闭览车抢案
Tour bus robbery. I've still got time.
和游览车抢案 我还有一点时间
Officers. Ma'am. Squeaker.
整察先生、女士、噶噶
- Cool! Ready for take-off! - What the...?
酷束了，淮人备出发 搞什么 ?
- Who are you supposed to be? - I'm IncrediBoy.
你是什么人 ? 我是超能小子呀
What? No.
什么 ? 不对
You're that kid from the fan club.
不对，你是我的小粉缘
Brophy. Brody. Buddy! Buddy!
布丁…布德…巴迪!
My name is IncrediBoy.
我的名字是超能小子
I've been nice, I've stood for photos,
区好，我很有耐心跟你合照
signed every scrap of paper you pushed at me...
每炎都帮你签名 可是这坎太遇份了…
No, don't worry about training me. I know your moves,
别担心，你不必训练我 你打击犯罪的每一个招式
crimefighting style, favorite catchphrases, everything!
连你的口头神我都会
I'm your number one fan!
我是你的头号粉缘耶
Hey! Hey, wait!
等一下
You know...
你知道吗 ?
.-you can tell a lot about a woman by the contents of her purse,
只要翻皮包就能瞳解一个女人
but maybe that's not what you had in mind.
不遇你好像另有目的
Hey, look...
列这柑
Elastigirl.
弹力女超人
Mr. Incredible.
超能先生
- It's all right. I've got him. - Sure, you've got him.
不用你操心，我会把他搞定 当然唾
- [took him out for you. - Sure, you did.
是我先把他所倒了 才怪
- His attention was on me. - A fact I exploited to do my job.
那是因和为他先被我听到 我就趁这个机会完成任务
- My job. - Asimple thank you will suffice.
这是我的任务 你只要说志谢讲就行了
Thanks, but I don't need any help.
谢了，不遇我不需要课忙
Whatever happened to "ladies first"?
你总了女士优先吗 ?
Whatever happened to equal treatment?
你总了男女平等吗 ?
Look, the lady got me first.
讲白公道话，女超人先摆倒我
- Well, we could share, you know. - L work alone.
我们可以一起分享功劳 我习惯一个人
Well, I think you need to be more...
我觉得你最好学会…
.. flexible.
…有加弹性
Are you doing anything later?
你待会有没有空 ?
Il have a previous engagement.
我已经有约了
Now, you just stay here.
乖乖待在这儿
They usually pick up the garbage in an hour.
一小时和后他们会来收过级
- Hey, Incredible! - Hey, Frozone!
超能先生 酷冰使
- Shouldn't you be getting ready? - [still got time.
你怎广膛不去准备?
He's gonna jump!
他要跳楼自
I think you broke something.
你害我摔断了和吧头
With counseling, I think you'll come to forgive me.
等你接受心理辅革以徐 就会原旋我
Wait a minute.
等一下
Bomb Voyage.
炸弹客
Mr. Incredible...!
超能先生
And IncrediBoy!
还有超能小子
IncrediBoy?
超能小子?
Aren't you curious about how I get around so fast? I have rocket boots.
你没想到我会这广快吧 ? 瞧，我穿了火箭订
- Go home, Buddy. Now. - What?
乎冬回家，快点 什么 ?
Little oaf...!
麻烦的小鬼
Can we talk?
我们能不能谈谈 ?
You always say be true to yourself,
你老是说要患庆自我
but you never say which part to be true to.
钾没说要患从自我的哪个部份
Well, I've finally figured out who I am. lam your ward... IncrediBoy!
我终人於找到真正的自我 我是你的小跟班，超能小子
And now, you have officially carried it too far, Buddy.
这灾你真的做得太通分了
This is because I don't have powers, isn't it?
你一定是嫌我没超人能力
Not every superhero has powers, you know. You can be super without them.
你不一定要有超人能力 没有超人能力也能当超级英雄
l invented these. I can fly. Can you fly?
这是我发明的 我会丧，你会吗 ?
Fly home, Buddy. I work alone.
赤回家吧，我习惯一个人
And your outfit is totally ridiculous!
你的超人装也超避的
Just give me one chance! I'll show you. I'll go get the police.
给我一次机会 我证明给你看，我去找警察
- Buddy, don't! - It'll only take a second.
巴迪，别去 只要一下子
No, stop! There's a bomb!
快回来，有枚炸弹
Let go, you're wrecking my flight pattern.
放手，你害我处不动了
- L can do this if you let go! - Will you just...?
让我放手去做 快下来
- I'm trying to help! Stop! - Let go of my cape!
我这是在帮你 放并我的披风
Take this one home. And make sure his mom knows what he's been doing.
把这小鬼送回家 告诉他妈他做了什么好事
I can help you. You're making a...
我可以攻你，你犯了大错
The injured jumper. You sent paramedics?
跳楼的像伙呢 ? 你叫了救访车吗 ?
They picked him up.
他们把他接走了
The blast in that building was caused by Bomb Voyage
那场爆炸是炸弹客搞的鬼
who I caught robbing the vault.
我还到他正在抢银行
We might nab him if we set up a perimeter.
派警力包园这儿就能还到他
- He got away? - Well, yeah.
他逃走了 ? 是啊
- Skippy here made sure of that. - IncrediBoy.
都是这麻烦的小鬼害的 我是超能小子
You're not affiliated with me! Holy smokes, I'm late.
列冒用我的名咏 惨了，我还到了
Listen, I've gotta be somewhere.
我得超去列的地方
- What about Bomb Voyage? - Any other night, I'd go after him,
炸弹客怎广办 ? 我平常非追到他不可
but I really gotta go. Don't worry. We'll get him! Eventually!
不遇我今天有事 放心，我们一定会还到他
- ls the night still young? - You're very late.
时间和膛早吧 ? 你差点就超不及
- How do I look? Good? - The mask. You still got the mask.
我看起来钙不钙 ? 等等，你的眼桔还没脱看
Showtime.
好厂上场
Robert Parr, will you have this woman to be your lawful wedded wife?
巴鸳伯，你顾意要她为要吐 ?
You're late. When you asked if l was doing anything later,
你膛到了 我以贺你刚才问我有汪有空
I didn't realize you'd forgotten. I thought it was playful banter.
只是开玩笑，没想到你都总了
You need to be more... flexible.
你最好要有点…弹性
I love you, but if we're gonna make this work,
我爱你，不遇如果你想机我
you've gotta be more than Mr. Incredible.
做的就要比超能先生更好
You know that. Don't you?
你原意吗 ?
- ..80 long as you both shall live? - ldo.
…永让互相扶持
I pronounce this couple husband and wife.
我宣布你们针为夫妻
As long as we both shall live. No matter what happens.
我们要永下互相扶持 不管发生什么事
Hey, come on. We're superheroes. What could happen?
拜旗，我们是超级英雄 会发生什么事 ?
for saving someone who didn't want to be saved.
竞然被对方告上法庭
The plaintiff, Oliver Sansweet,
原告桶奥佛
who was foiled in his attempted suicide by Mr. Incredible,
试图跳楼自杀时 被超能先生阻正
has filed suit against the famed superhero in Superior Court.
僚是向这位超级英雄提出告诉
Mr. Sansweet didn't ask to be saved. He didn't want to be saved.
又先生冰没有要求被救 他也不想被救
The injury received from Mr. Incredible's "actions",
超能先生的恶行恶状 害他受重伤
- causes him daily pain. - saved your life!
每天都痛得要命 我救了你这人条小命耶
You didn't save my life! You ruined my death.
才没有 你破壤了我寻死的好事
My client has no further comment.
我的当事人把可牵告
Five days later, another suit was filed by the victims of the el train accident.
五天和后，捷运意外的受害者 也向超能先生要求赔倘
Incredible's court losses cost the government millions.
这些官司让政府付出数百蕊元
And opened the floodgates for dozens of superhero lawsuits the world over.
世界各地的超级英雄 也接二连三被告上法院
It is time for their secret identity to become their only identity.
他们的秘密身份 应该成为他们唯一的身份
Time for them to join us, or go away.
他们不加入正常人的行列 就玖我们越速越好
Under tremendous pressure, and the crushing financial burden
在强大的社会仁论 以及一连串求俩案件
of an ever mounting series of lawsuits,
巨大的财务压力下
in exchange for the promise to never again resume hero work.
但是他们要保证 永这不再行侠仗义
Where are they now?
他们现在在哪里?
They are living among us. Average citizens, average heroes.
他们跟我们一起生活 平凡的老百姓，平凡的英雄
Quietly and anonymously continuing to make the world a better place.
为了维持世界安全与和平 隐姓理名、销声匿踊
Denied? You're denying my claim?
不批准? 你拒绝支付保险金给我 ?
I don't understand. I have full coverage.
我不懂，我有全额保险耶
I'm sorry, Mrs. Hogenson,
很抱菊，何太太 不遇您的保踢上第17季 (二五年后 )
Excuse me. Claims, Bob Parr.
对不起 申报部，巴锡伯
I'm calling to celebrate a momentous occasion.
今天要庆祝一个重要的日子
We're now officially moved in.
我们正式搬进来了
Yeah, well, that's great, honey.
太好了，老婆
The last three years don't count because...
这三年为什么都不算呢 ?
- Why do we have so much junk? - Listen, I've got a client.
家壬怎广这广多垃圾 ? 凰好，我有客户
Say no more. Go save the world one policy at a time, honey.
我明白了 你就去拯救需要保险的人吧
I gotta go pick up the kids. See you tonight.
我得去接孩子们下课了 晚上网
Bye, honey. Excuse me. Where were we?
拜了，老婆 抱娄，我讲到哪儿 ?
I'm on a fixed income, and if you can't help me,
我的收入有有限，如果你不帮忙
I don't know what I'll do.
我就不知道该怎广办
Listen closely. I'd like to help you, but I can't.
仔细孤好 我很想帮人，可是我不能
I'd like to say take a copy of your policy to Norma Wilcox on...
我很想叫你把保重拿给魏诺天
Norma Wilcox. W-I-L-C-O-X. On the third floor. But I can't.
义仆、魏诺珊 她在三楼，不过我不能
l also do not advise you to fill out and file a WS2475 form
我也不能建议虹到二楼法律部
with our legal department on the second floor.
填一张WS-2475表格
l wouldn't expect someone to get back to you quickly to resolve the matter.
这件事也不会这广快就解决
Parr!
姓巴的
You authorized payment on the Walker policy!
你批准华家的保险金给付 ?
Someone broke into their house, Mr. Huph.
他们家唱小偷，享先生
- Their policy covers... - [don't wanna know about it.
保单上明明说… 我不想知道
Don't tell me about it. Tell me how you're keeping Insuricare in the black.
列跟我说，我只想知道 随便什么阿畦阿狗向你求情
Tell me how that's possible, with you writing checks
你就装好人答应要付绥给他们
to every Harry Hardluck and Sally Sobstory that calls you.
这样要怎床训公司赚钱哆?
Morning break is over.
休息时间针束
l appreciate you coming down here, Mrs. Parr.
巴太太，府谢人超来
What's this about? Has Dash done something wrong?
发生什么事 ? 小屎做错事吗 ?
He's a disruptive influence and he openly mocks me in front of the class.
他是个款榜样 他在全班同学面前让我出粮
- He says. - Look, I know it's you!
他乱议 我知道是你
- He puts thumbtacks on my stool. - You saw him do this?
他在我椅子上放大头舍 你看到是他做的咀?
Well... not really. No.
这个疗…其实呢…
Actually, not.
苍没有
Oh, then how do you know it was him?
那你怎广知道是他 ?
l hid a camera. Yeah, and this time, I've got him.
我装了摄影机，这还到他了
See? You see?
瞧，你们看到吐?
You don't see it?
你们没看到 ?
He moves! Right there!
他动了一下，那儿
Wait, wait! Right there!
等等，那儿
Right as I'm sitting down!
就在我坐下来的时候
don't know how he does it,
我不知道他怎广弄的
but there's no tack before he moves
不遇他动之前没有大头针
and after he moves, there's a tack. Coincidence? I think not!
之后就有大闫人针了 这是巧合叶 ?站不是
- Bernie... - Don't "Bernie" me.
班尼 列叫我班尼
This little rat is guilty!
这个小鬼有罪
You and your son can go now, Mrs. Parr. I'm sorry for the trouble.
巴太太，你们可以走了 很抱火麻烦你跑一趟
You're letting him go again? He's guilty!
你又要放他走? 他明明腊
You can see it on his smug little face. Guilty, I say, guilty!
他一直在偷笑 他有罪，他有罪
Dash, this is the third time this year you've been sent to the office.
小冻，这是你今年 第三次被叫进校长室
We need to find a better outlet. A more... constructive outlet.
你得找别的方法发漫情绪 更有建设性的发小管道
Maybe I could, if you'd let me go out for sports.
你只要让我参加有运动比赛就行
Honey, you know why we can't do that.
你明明知道不行
I promise I'll slow up. I'll only be the best by a tiny bit.
我答应会跑慢一点 我只会赢一点儿
Dashiell Robert Parr,
巴小飞
you are an incredibly competitive boy. And a bit of a showoff.
你的好腾心很强，也很党现
The last thing you need is temptation.
你一定受不了诱惑
You always say, "Do your best." But you don't really mean it.
人老是叫我全力以赴 可是你都是在骗人
Why can't I do the best that I can do?
我为什么不能全力以赴?
Right now, the world wants us to fit in, so we gotta be like everybody else.
现在社会要我们当正常人 我们就得跟列人一样
Dad said our powers were nothing to be ashamed of.
爸说我们不应该 以我们的超能力为了
- Our powers made us special. - Everyone's special, Dash.
起能力让我们特别 每个人都很特别，小飞
Which is another way of saying no one is.
意思就是没有人是特别的
Hey, Rydinger, where you headed?
旬同学，你要去哪里 ?
- Hi, Tony. - Hey.
，混尼 螺
- Hey, Tony, can I carry your books? - That's kind of funny.
汤尼，让人家加你拿书嘛 不好笑
Hey, Tony, do you play football?
汤尼，你想打球吗 ?
Tony, I thought we were . . gonna go swimming.
温尼，我们不是要 一起去游泳吗 ?
He looked at me.
他看了我一限
Come on, Violet!
快点啦，小傅
Darn kids. Sitting on the driveway...
讨灰的小提 老是在我的车道上玩
Oh, great.
这下好了
Mom.
杂?
- You're making weird faces again. - No, I'm not.
娩又在做鬼脸了 才没有
You make weird faces, honey.
人在做锡脸，老婆
- Do you have to read at the table? - Yeah.
你一定要看报吐 ? 对
Bob, could you help the carnivore cut his meat?
老公，提这个肉食动物切 肉
Dash, you have something you wanna tell your father about school?
小飞 跟和苞和爸说你今天做了什么
- Well, we dissected a frog. - Dash got sent to the office again.
我们在课堂上解剖青蛙 小丫又被叫到校长室
- Good. Good. - No, Bob, that's bad.
很好啊，很好 这冰不好
- What? - Dash got sent to the office again.
什么 ? 小丫又被叫到校长室
- What?! What for? - Nothing.
为什么 ? 没锅什么
He put a tack on the teacher's chair... during class.
他上课晨 在老师椅子上放大头针
Nobody saw me. You could barely see it on the tape.
浊有人看到 华影带上看不到我
They caught you on tape and you still got away with it?
你被拍到可是没被带到 ?
You must have been booking. How fast were you going?
你一定超快的，你有多快?
We are not encouraging this.
请你别鼓励他
I'm not, I'm just asking how fast...
疮没有啊，我只是问他多快
Honey!
老公
Great. First the car, now I gotta pay to fix the table...
太好了，先是车子 现在又这样
What happened to the car?
车耶? 车子怎广了?
Here. I'm getting a new plate.
我去拿新的盘子
So, how about you, Vi? How was school?
你呢，小倩?学校玩好吗 ?
- Nothing to report. - You've hardly touched your food.
没什么特列的 你速一口都没有吃
- I'm not hungry for meatloaf. - Well, it is leftover night.
我不爱吃肉饼 今天吃剩菜
We have steak, pasta... What are you hungry for?
有牛排和义大利类 你到底想要什科 ?
- Tony Rydinger. - Shut up.
雪混尼 于并
- Well, you are. - l said, shut up, you little insect.
我叫你并嘴，小不点儿
- Well, she is. - Do not shout at the table.
她真的很哈他 不要在餐桌上吵架
- Honey! - Kids! Listen to your mother.
老公 ? 孩子们，台妈妈的话
She'd eat if we were having Tony loaf.
有雷混尼在她什么都吃得下
That's it!
我受金了
Stop it!
列关了
- You're gonna be toast! - Stop running in the house.
人死定了 列在屋里跑来跑去
Sit down!
坐下来
- Hey, no force fields! - You started it.
不准用防访罩 是你先车我的
You sit down! You sit down!
给我坐好，坐下来
Violet!
小依!
Simon J. Paladino,
帕赛门下落不明
longtime advocate of superhero rights, is missing?
(失距人口)
- Gazerbeam. - Bob! It's time to engage.
老公，快来啊
Do something! Don't just stand there!
别光站在那儿
- [need you to intervene! - You want me to intervene?
快来帮忙呀 你要我帮忙 ?
Okay. I'm intervening!
好，我就来帮忙
Violet, let go of your brother.
小倩，把弟弟放开
Hello?
哈唾
Get the door.
去开门
- Hey, Lucius! - Hey, Speedo. Helen, Vi, Jack-Jack.
酷冰侠叔叔 飞毛腿、荷莉、小傅、小代
- Ice of you to drop by. - Never heard that one before.
今天什笨冰把你吹来 ? 这笑话有锡冷
Lucius!
酷冰侠叔叔
- [like it when it shatters. - I'll be back later.
我比较喜数碎冰 我会晚点回来
- Where are you two going? - It's Wednesday.
你们要去哪儿 ? 今天是礼拜三
Bowling night. Say hello to Honey for me, Lucius.
路易，替我跟大嫂问好
Will do. Good night, Helen. Good night, kids.
好，晚安，荷痢 晚安，孩子们
Don't think you've avoided talking about the principal's office.
别以篇你被叫到校长室 这件事就这样算了
Your father and I are still gonna discuss it.
我会跟你和爸商量该怎广处习你
I'm not the only kid who's been sent to the office.
别的小朋友也有被叫进校长室
Other kids don't have superpowers.
别的小朋友没有超人能力
- Now, it's perfectly normal... - What do you know about normal?
正常的小孩… 人知道什么是正常吐 ?
What does anyone in this family know about normal?
我们家有人知道 什么是正常吗 ?
- Now, wait a minute, young lady. - We act normal. l wanna be normal.
列这广激动 我不想假装，我想当正常人
The only normal one is Jack-Jack, and he's not even toilet trained.
只有小傈才正常 可是他还在包尿布
Lucky.
算他幸还
l meant about being normal.
我是说他很正常
So now I'm in deep trouble.
那一炊我差点就没命
I mean, one more jolt of this death ray and I'm an epitaph.
他再射一道死光，我就死定了
Somehow I managed to find cover. What does Baron Von Ruthless do?
幸好我躲过了 你知道他做什么吐?
- He starts monologuing.
他开始哈独和白 他开始哈一段独白
He starts this prepared speech about how feeble l am compared to him.
他照著稿子开始说我有多忱
How inevitable my defeat is, the world will soon be his. Yada, yada, yada.
我注定会死在他手里 他很快就能狼治世界什么的
I mean, the guy has me on a platter, and he won't shut up.
那父伙已经还到我了 还不此乖冬并嘴
- Three Municiberg, we have a 23-56... - 23-56, what is that?
费蒙街发生2356状涡 那是什么状况 ?
- Robbery? - This is just sad.
抢案吗 ? 这太可斐了
- Want to catch a robber? - No.
你想抓抢菲吗 ?
Tell you the truth, I'd rather go bowling.
老实说，我宁愿去打保戴球
Look, what if we actually did what our wives think we're doing?
这炊咱们不如真的去打保夫球
Just to shake things up.
这样还比较刺激
He's not alone. The fat guy's still with him.
他不是一个人，那胖子在党尊
They're just talking.
他们只是在哈啦打忆
- What are we doing here? - Protecting people.
我们这是在干六 ? 保护人民安全
- Nobody asked us. - You need an invitation?
没人请我们保护他们 你需要请帖吗 ?
I'd like one, yes. We keep sneaking out to do this, and...
是啊，有请帖最好
- You remember Gazerbeam? - There was something in the paper.
你记得激光使吗 ? 今天报上有他的新闻
- He had trouble with civilian life. - When did you see him?
他也不习惯遇正常生活 你竹时看通他 ?
I don't see anyone from the old days. Just you.
我跟这些老采伴都没来往 只有你
- And we're pushing our luck as it is. - Come on.
其实这样挺冒险的 列抬惧癖
It was fun the first time, but if we keep doing this...
第一妇还可以 要是继续下去就会…
- We have a report on a fire... - Afire. We're close!
四街发生火火 火炎，有搞头了
- Yeah, baby! - We're gonna get caught.
好耶 ! 我们会被还到
Fire! Yeah!
火货 ! 好耶!
- ls that everybody? - Yeah, that's everyone.
人都救到了吗 ? 对，都救到了
- It better be. - Can't you put this out?
最好是 你不能用冰把火涛熄吗 ?
I can't lay down a layer thick enough! It's evaporating too fast!
不行啦，我做的冰不兔厚 马上就会融化蒸发
- What's that mean? - It means it's hot.
那是什么意思 ? 这儿太热了
- I'm dehydrated, Bob. - You're out of ice?
我快腕水了 你的冰用完了?
You can't run out. You can use water in the air.
不可能啦 你能用空气中的水份
There is no water in this air! What's your excuse, run out of muscle?
这儿的空气根本浊有水份 你的力气也用完了吐 ?
I can't smash walls. The building's getting weaker.
我不能撞义而出 这标房子太脆弱了
- It's gonna come down on top of us. - lL wanted to go bowling!
一撞就会被撞倒 我本来想去打保协球的
All right! Stay right on my tail! This is gonna get hot!
跟著我来，这会很车险
- We look like incompetent bad guys! - You can get water out of the air.
我们活像一对策赋 你可以从空气中青出冰才
Freeze!
列动
- I'm thirsty. - l said freeze!
我口渴 我叫你列动
I'm just getting a drink.
我只是想喝口水
- You've had your drink. Now... - [ know. I know. Freeze.
好，你喝完了就冬乖… 我知道…我会让你钻姜
Police officers!
这是警察
That was way too close.
刚才好险哦
We are not doing that again.
下炊我绝对不干了
Verify you want to switch targets? Over.
人要换另一个目标吐?
Trust me. This is the one he's been looking for.
相信我，他找的就是这一个
- [thought you'd be back by 11. - [said I'd be back later.
我以高你十一点就会回家 我说我会晚点回家
l assumed you'd be back later. If you came back at all...
我当然知道 如果你会回来的话
- .. you'd be "back later". - Well, I'm back, okay?
背定就是晚一哑 我这不是回来了吗 ?
Is this rubble?
这是瓦碟吗?
It was just a little workout. Just to stay loose.
我只是暖暖身，放到蔡
You know how I feel about that. Darn you! We can't blow cover again.
你明知道我反对，真是的 我们不能再曝露身份
- The building was coming down anyway. - What?
反正那棣房子一定会倒韦 什么 ?
You knocked down a building?
你撞倒一标房子?
It was on fire. Structurally unsound. It was coming down.
屋子起火，很危险 反正一定会倒塌
Have you been listening to the police scanner again?
列跟我说你又去 偷匠警方着缚电了
I performed a public service. You act like that's bad.
我是去救人耶，这又不是玉事
Itis a bad thing, Bob!
这是壕事
Uprooting our family again, so you can relive the glory days is a bad thing.
为了重温得萝害我们又要搬家
It's better than acting like they didn't happen!
这名比假装只是一场葛来得好
Yes! They happened! But this, our family,
没错，那闪不是一场萝 不明现在我们的家庭
is what's happening now, Bob. You are missing this!
才是最重要的事 而你名错遇了一切
I can't believe you don't want to go to your own son's graduation.
你连小屎的蛙业典礼都不此去
It's not a graduation. He's moving from fourth to fifth grade.
那不是晒业典礼 他只是从四年级升到五年级
- It's a ceremony! - It's psychotic!
那是个庆祝仪式 那是胡扯淡
They keep creating new ways to celebrate mediocrity
他们一直想新的办法 庆祝平凡的事
but if someone is exceptional...
但是当一个人撞有超凡的能力
This is not about you, Bob. It's about Dash.
我是在说小习，别扯到你身上
You want to do something for Dash? Let him actually compete.
你想让小屎高绍? 那就让他参加比赛
- Let him go out for sports! - [ will not be the enemy!
让他参加运动就赛 别让我当壤人
- You know why we can't. - Because he'd be great.
你明知道他篇什么不能 因为他一定会赢
This is not about you!
这不是关於你…
All right, Dash. I know you're listening. Come on out.
小站，我知道你在偷取 出来吧
Vi? You, too, young lady.
小倩 ? 刀一样
It's okay, kids. We're just having a discussion.
没事了，我们只是在谈事情
Pretty loud discussion.
册起来像是吵和架
But that's okay. What's important is that Mommy and I are a team.
没关像，重要的是 我跟杂怒是站在同一比的
- We're united against the forces of... - Pigheadedness?
我们一向都揣手对抗… 顽国的心驴 ?
- lwas gonna say evil. - We're sorry we woke you.
我本来想说邪恶力量 抱娄把你们吵醒
Everything's okay. Go back to bed. It's late.
没事了 回去睡觉吧，很晚了
- Good night, Mom. Night, Dad. - Good night.
晚安，和区、妈 晚安
In fact, we should all be in bed.
我们都回去皮觉吧
Request claim on claim numbers 158183...
158183号保单要求申报
Haven't you got him yet? Where is he?
去叫他，他在哪儿 ?
Mr. Huph would like to talk to you in his office.
享先生要网你
- Now? - Now.
现在吐? 现在
Sit down, Bob.
鸳伯，坐下来
I'm not happy, Bob. Not happy.
我很不爽哦，我超不更的
- Ask me why. - Okay. Why?
问我高什么 好，痪什么 ?
Why what? Be specific, Bob.
为什么什么 ? 问清楚
Why are you unhappy?
你加什么不歌 ?
Your customers make me unhappy.
你的客户让我很不殉
What, you've gotten complaints?
你收到投诉吗 ?
Complaints I can handle.
投诉我才不怕
What I can't handle is your customers’ inexplicable knowledge
我怕的是你的客户莫名其妙
of Insuricare's inner workings! They're experts. Experts, Bob!
都了解保险公司如何运作 他们都爸成保险专家
Exploiting every loophole, dodging every obstacle!
氏保单的漏洞，估我的便宜
They're penetrating the bureaucracy!
他们突破了公司的属属关卡
- Did I do something illegal? - No.
我有犯法吗 ? 没有
- We shouldn't help our customers? - The law requires that l answer no.
我们不该帮助客户吗? 根据法律我得说不是
- We're supposed to help people. - Help our people!
我们本来就证该帮助人 帮助我们自己人
Starting with our stockholders.
先从公司股东开始
Who's helping them out, huh?
谁来帮助他们 ?
You know, Bob, a company...
鸳伯，你要知道 一间公司…
Is like an enormous clock.
就像一个巨大的时人甸
..1S like an enormous... Yes. Precisely.
就像一个巨大的… 对，没错
It only works if all the little cogs mesh together.
每一个零件都要正常运作
Now, a clock needs to be cleaned, well-lubricated and wound tight.
一个时尔要定时清江 上油、上紧发条
The best clocks have jewel movements, cogs that fit, that cooperate by design.
最好的时甸撞有完美的机蕊 以及经遇互相配合的零件
I'm being metaphorical, Bob. Know what I mean by cooperative cogs?
我这是比喻，鸳伯 你应该了解我在说什么吧 ?
Bob?
鲍伯?
Bob? Look at me when I'm talking to you, Parr.
我跟你讲话要看著我
- That man out there, he needs help. - Don't change the subject.
那个人需要旭助 列顾左右而言他
- We're discussing your attitude. - He's getting mugged!
我在跟你讲话 他被抢劫了
- Let's hope we don't cover him. - I'll be right back.
他最好没有保险 我马上回来
Stop right now or you're fired!
你不站住我就并除你
Close the door.
把门关上
Get over here, now.
给我明来
I'm not happy, Bob. Not happy.
我很不碍，超不更的
- He got away. - Good thing, too.
他逃走了 那季好
You were this close to losing your...
你差哑就去掉饭…
Please report to operating room 722 immediately.
请立即到722约手术和羽
- How is he? - He'll live.
他还好吧 ? 死不了
- I'm fired, aren't I? - You think?
我被并除了吗 ? 那还用说
- What can I say, Rick? - Nothing you haven't said before.
我能说什么 ? 你能说的早就说了
- Someone was in trouble. - Always.
有人遇到麻烦 天天都有麻烦
- [had to do something. - Every time you say that,
我一定要提助他们 你每次这广说
it's a month and a half of trouble for me.
我就得花和化个月替你探屁股
Hundreds of thousands of taxpayer's dollars.
浪费仇十菌元公委
- l know. - We pay to keep the company quiet.
我知道 我得赔线给你的公司
We pay damages, erase memories, relocate your family.
消除员工记居，旭你搬新家
Every time it gets harder. Money, money, money.
每炎都越来越麻烦 花色像流水一样
We can't keep doing this. We appreciate what you did in the old days,
我们不能一直继续下去 我们很感激你过去的贡献
but those days are over. From now on, you're on your own.
不遇到此痪止 你往和后要靠自己
Listen, Bob. Maybe I could relocate you, you know, for old times' sake.
这样吧，也许我能用你搬家 看在老交情份上
I can't do that to my family. Everyone just got settled.
我不能这广对我的家人 他们都安顿好了
I'll make it work. Thanks.
我会想办法，谢了
Take care of yourself.
你自己要保重
What are you waiting for?
你在等什么 ?
I don't know. Something amazing, I guess.
不知道，发生什么奇踊吧
Me, too, kid.
我也是
"Hold still"?
列动 ?
Match: Mr. Incredible.
身份确认 : 超能先生
Room is secure. Commence message.
房间安全，开始播放留言
Hello, Mr. Incredible. Yes, we know who you are.
你好，超能先生 是的，我们知道你是谁
Rest assured, your secret is safe with us.
请放心，我们不会波密
My name is Mirage. We have something in common.
我叫幻影，我跟你一样
According to the government, neither of us exist.
根据政府记录，我们都不存在
Please pay attention, as this message is classified and will not be repeated.
请仔细又，这是最高机密 我不会再说第二遍
! represent a top secret division of the government,
我代表一个机密政府单位
designing and testing experimental technology,
进行一项实验性科技研究
and we have need of your unique abilities.
我们必须借重你的超能力
Something happened at our testing facility.
发生了一起意外
- Honey! - What?
老公 ? 干乌?
- Dinner's ready. - Okay.
开饭了 好
.{t's contained within an isolated area,
有一个机器人失去控制
it threatens to cause incalculable damage to itself and our facilities,
很可能摧毁它自己 以及我们的实验基地
jeopardizing hundreds of millions of dollars...
站危害价值数百菌元的设备
Is someone in there?
有人在里面吗?
- It's the TV, trying to watch. - Because of its sensitive nature...
我正在看电视. 这是一项高难度任务
- Stop trying. It's time for dinner. - One minute!
列看了，出来吃饭 等一下
If you accept, your payment will be triple your current annual salary.
所以酬劳会比你 目前的年薪多三倍
Call the number on the card. Voice-matching will ensure security.
请打名片上的电话张硒 语音识别系统能篇你保密
The supers aren't gone, Mr. Incredible. You're still here.
超人特攻队站洛有解散 你还在这儿
You can still do great things. Or...
你可以做出伟大贡献
..you can listen to police scanners. Your choice.
或是去偷匠警方乱线志 这是你的选择
You have 24 hours to respond.
请在24小时内答履
Think about it
仔细考虑看看
You are one distracted guy.
你真是个破壤王
Am I? I don't mean to be.
是吗 ?我不是故意的
I know you miss being a hero and your job is frustrating.
我知道你怀念当一个英雄 你的工作也很没有前途
I want you to know how much it means to me that you stay at it anyway.
不遇我只希望你能多续工作
- Honey? About the job? - What?
老婆，关於我的工作 怎订了 ?
- Something's happened.
发生了一件事 什么事 ?
- The... - What?
呢…-
The company is sending me to a conference.
公司派我去并会
- Aconference? - Out of town.
开会 ? 到外地开会
I'm gonna be gone for a few days.
我要到外地出差疲天
They've never sent you to a conference before. This is good, isn't it?
他们从来没派你去开会 这是好事，不是吗 ?
Yes.
是啊
You see? They're finally recognizing your talents.
你看吧 你的才能余於得到赏识
- You're moving up. - Yes.
你要升官了 是啊
- Honey! This is wonderful! - Yes, it is.
这真是太好了
Hello?
咀?
This is Mr. Incredible.
这是超能先生
I'm in.
我要加入
The Omnidroid 9000 is a top secret prototype battle robot.
全能机器人九千号 是最高机密战站机器人原型
Its artificial intelligence enables it to solve any problem
它撞有先进的人工智慧 能久解决任何问题
it's confronted with. And, unfortunately...
不幸的是…
Let me guess. It got smart enough to wonder why it had to take orders.
让我猜 它变得太隐明，不此乖冬匠话
We lost control. Now it's loose in the jungle, threatening our facility.
它失去控制，在王林到处和六落 对实验基地造成威鲁
We've had to evacuate all personnel from the island for their own safety.
我们必须将所有人员搬歼小岛
How am I going in?
我要怎广下去 ?
The Omnidroid's defenses necessitate an air drop from 5000 feet.
你得从五千英只高空 降落小岛执行任务
Its cloaking devices make it difficult to track.
它有隐形装置，很准追中
We're pretty sure it's on the southern half of the island.
不遇我们很确定它在小岛南遵
One more thing. Obviously it represents a significant investment.
还有一件事，它是昂贵的投资
You want me to shut it down without destroying it.
人要我把它天掉 不能把它毁掉
You are Mr. Incredible.
你真的是超能先生
I've got to warn you, it's a learning robot.
我得警告你 它的学习能力很强
Every moment you fight it increases its knowledge of how to beat you.
它能在打浆遇程中 学会怎广打败你
Shut it down. Do it quickly. Don't destroy it.
亿快明太它，不要毁了它
- And don't die. - Great. Thanks.
也不要丢了小命 好极了，谢了
Showtime.
好厂上场
My back!
我的苛
Surprising. We must bring him back.
真没想到，把他带回来
Sound the all clear, and invite him to dinner.
通知他任务完成，请他吃晚僻
Praise him. Make him feel like we appreciate his abilities.
座奖他做名 让他觉得我们很欣赏他
Am I overdressed?
我穿得太正式了吗 ?
Actually, you look rather dashing.
不会，你看起来很钟
- [ take it our host is... - I'm sorry.
我猜我们的主人… 很抱娄
He won't be dining with us. He hopes you'll understand.
他有事不能来 他希望你能这解
Of course. I do usually make it a point to know who I'm working for.
当然了 不明我很想知道我替谁工作
He prefers a certain amount of anonymity.
他希望隐藏自己的身份
Surely, you of all people understand that.
你一定能角了解
Il was just wondering, of all the places to settle down, why live...
我只是好奇，有这广多地方 他篇什么要住在…
With a volcano? He's attracted to power. Soaml.
火山劣遵 ? 他喜欢挑战，我也一样
- It's a weakness we share. - Seems a bit unstable.
这是我们俩的弱点 火山很危险
I prefer to think of it as misunderstood.
我倒觉得这是个误解
Aren't we all?
大家都是?
Volcanic soil is among the most fertile on Earth.
火山党的土壤非常肥沃
Everything at the table was grown right here.
每赚食物都是在这儿种的
- How does it compare? - Everything's delicious.
你觉得如何 ? 每道菜都很好吃
Or you'll be late for work.
你上班要膛到了
- Have a great day, honey. - Thanks.
祝你上班愉快 谢了
- Help customers, climb ladders... - Bring bacon.
者助客户，升官发财 闵家糊口 ?
All that jazz.
一点也没错
You have an appointment?
你有预约吐?
I'm an old friend. I just wanted to...
我是个老朋友，我只想…
- All visitors are required... - Go check the electric fence.
访客必须… 去检查电样栏 !
What is it? Who are you? What do you want?
你是谁?你想干咏 ?
My God, you've gotten fat. Come in. Come, come.
我的天，你怎订变这广胖 ? 进来，进来
Yes, things are going quite well. Quite well. My God, no complaints.
是啊，我的事业很成功 没什么好抱怨的
But, you know, it is not the same. Not the same at all.
不遇跟以前不一样 完全没得比
Weren't you in the news? Some show in Prague?
称不是上了新闻 在布拉格开时装秀吗 ?
Milan, darling. Milan.
是米兰，亲爱的
Supermodels. Nothing super about them.
超级名模 她们一点都不超级
Spoiled, stupid, little stick figures
全都是被媒体窗壤的瘦儿竿
with poofy lips who think only about themselves.
限里只有她们自己
l used to design for gods.
我曾经禹天神设计服装
But perhaps you come with a challenge? Il was surprised to get your call.
你是来带给我新的挑战吗 ? 接到你电话我嘛了一跳
E, I just need a patch job.
克夫人 我只是想请你补个洞
This is megamesh. Outmoded, but very sturdy.
超能装，遇时了，但很耐穿
And you've torn right through it! What have you been doing, Robert?
被你再破了一个洞 你都在干桨呀，鸳伯?
Moonlighting hero work?
偷偷干英雄匀当吐?
Must have happened a long time ago.
一定是很久以前弄破的
Il see. This is a hobo suit, darling.
是吐?这是件灿衣服
You can't be seen in this. I won't allow it!
你不能穿著它趴趴走 我不准
- Fifteen years ago, maybe, but now? - What do you mean? You designed it.
十五年前可以，现在休想 这是你设计的耶
I never look back, darling. It distracts from the now.
我从不看明去，免得影响现在
You need a new suit. That much is certain.
你需要全新的超能装
Where the heck am I gonna get a new suit?
全新的超能装 ? 我要找谁攻我做呢?
You can't! It's impossible! I'm far too busy.
不行，我太忙了
So ask me now, before l again become sane.
趁我还没忙到发疯 赶快求我帮你做
Wait. You want to make me a suit?
等等，虹要者我做超能装 ?
You push too hard, darling! But I accept.
你的要求太遇份了 不明我答应
- It will be bold. Dramatic! - Yeah.
设计大脆前本 好
- Heroic! - Yeah, something classic, like Dynaguy!
充满英雄气概 优雅耐看，就跟爆破侠一样
He had a great look! Oh, the cape and the boots...
他的造型钙洒了，披居配长凌
No capes!
不要披必
- Isn't that my decision? - Do you remember Thunderhead?
这不是由我决定吗 ? 你记得雷必使吗 ?
Tall, storm powers. Nice man. Good with kids.
高大英插、呼几唤十 好人一个，超爱小孩的
- Listen, E... - November 15th of '58.
职我说 1958年11月15日
Alf was well, another day saved when his cape snagged on a missile fin.
他又郁救了世界 后来他的披风被屎弹久到
Thunderhead was not the brightest bulb...
雷风侠不是很隐明
Stratogale!
风暴女
April 23rd, '57. Cape caught in a jet turbine.
1957年4月23日 披风被措进喷射引擎
You can't generalize about these things.
称不能以偏概全
Splashdown, sucked into a vortex. No capes!
水花侠，被湾渴皂走 不要披属 !
You know I'm retired from hero work.
炼明知道我已经退出江湖了
As am I, Robert. Yet, here we are.
我也是，那又怎样 ?
E, l only need a patch job. For sentimental reasons.
我只想博你终好破洞 这很有纪念价值
Fine. I will also fix the hobo suit.
好啦，我就顺便划你补破洞
- You're the best of the best, E. - Yes, I know, darling. I know.
你最术了，衣夫人 我知道，亲过的
Don't answer it, honey, I got it!
我来搂，老玫，列接
- Hello? - We have a new assignment for you.
咀? 你有一项新任务
- How soon can you get here? - I'll leave tomorrow morning.
你几时能到 ? 我明天就出发
- See you there. - Goodbye.
到时候见 拜了
Who was that, honey? The office?
那是谁?公司吐?
Another conference. Short notice, but you know...
我又要去开会，有点直
..duty calls.
不遇没办法
- Bob? - Yeah, what's up, honey?
老公 ? 有什么事吗 ?
- Have a great trip. - Thanks, sweetie.
祝你旅途愉快 谢了
- I'll call you when I get there. - [love you.
我到了会打给你 我爱你
- So much. - [love you too.
我好爱你 我也很爱姓
This is your automated Captain.
这是自动蜀鞭机长
Would you care for more mimosa?
再来一杯酒吗 ?
- Don't mind if do. Thanks. - You're welcome.
当然好，谢了 不客气
Currently 78 degrees in Nomanisan. Perfect weather for flying.
诺曼尼岛目前摄氏26度 最壕合飞行
Please fasten your seat belt. We're beginning our descent.
请吉好安全带，我们准备下降
- Hello, Mr. Incredible. Nice suit. - Thanks.
你好，好炫的超能装 谢了
Nice to be back, Mirage.
很高要能回来，幻影
You'll be briefed on your assignment in the conference room at two.
请你下午雨点 到会议宝职到任务简报
- D Wing, room A-113. - 2:00. Got it.
D标、A-113室 雨点钾，没问题
See you there.
到时候见
Edna.
衣娜
- I'd like to speak to Edna, please. - This is Edna.
我找衣娜 我就是衣娜
- E? This is Helen. - Helen who?
衣夫人，我是荷莉 哪个荷莉 ?
Helen Parr? You know...
巴荷莉，知道嘛
Elastigirl?
弹力女超人
Darling! It's been such a long time after all these years! So long!
厅爱的，好久没联络了
Yes, it's been a while. Listen.
是啊，是有一阵子了
There's only one person Bob would trust to patch his supersuit. That's you.
鸳伯只会找一个人补超能装 那就是你衣夫人
Yes, yes, yes. Marvelous, isn't it?
没错，超误的，对吧 ?
Much better than those horrible pajamas he used to wear.
比他以前穿的糯睡衣好多了
They are finished. When are you coming to see?
都做好了，姓时来看 ?
- I'm calling about... - Don't make me beg.
我是打来则… 别逼我求你
- L won't do it, you know. - Beg, no, I'm calling about suit.
我才不干 我不是求你打来…逼你…
About Bob's suit! I'm calling about Bob's suit.
我是打来问锡伯的超能装
You come in one hour, darling. linsist, okay? Okay. Goodbye.
一小时后，一定要来 就这样唾，再网
It's bigger!
体积更订大
It's badder!
威力更强大
Ladies and gentlemen, it's too much for Mr. Incredible!
各位先生女士 它连超能先生都能打败
You know, I went through quite a few supers to get it worthy to fight you,
在你之前我拿很多超人试遇
but man, it wasn't good enough!
可是它上灵印被你打持
After you trashed the last one, l had to make some major modifications.
你把它打持以后我就重新改装
Sure it was difficult, but you are worth it.
很不容易，但是很值得
l mean, after all, lam your biggest fan.
时竟哆 我是你最大的粉缘
- Buddy? - My name is not Buddy!
巴迪 ? 我的名字不是巴迪
And it's not IncrediBoy either!
也不是超能小子
That ship has sailed. All l wanted was to help you.
我不屑当超能小子了 当年我只想攻你
l only wanted to help! And what did you say to me?
我想帮忙，你务怎庆说 ?
Fly home, Buddy. I work alone.
赤回家吧，我习惯一个人
It tore me apart. But I learned an important lesson.
你伤透了我的心 不遇我学到一个教训
You can't count on anyone.
你不能靠任何人
Especially your heroes.
尤其是你的英雄偶像
l was wrong to treat you that way. I'm sorry.
我不该那广对你，对不起
See? Now you respect me, because I'm a threat.
瞧，现在你就怕我了 因为我很强
That's the way it works.
人都很现实
There's a lot of people, whole countries who want respect.
有很多国家都想要爸强
And they will pay through the nose to get it.
他们贺了伙得强大原意付天价
How do you think I got rich? l invented weapons.
你以贺我是怎广发财的 ? 靠发明各种武器
Now I have a weapon only I can defeat. And when I unleash it, I'll get...
这具机器人只有我能对付
You sly dog! You got me monologuing.
你真狐独 你害我一直在哈独和白
I can't believe it.
我不敢相信
It's cool, huh? Zero-point energy.
很酷吧?零点能量光
I save the best inventions for myself.
我把最棒的发明留给自己
Am I good enough now?
我现在级棒了吧 ?
Who's super now?
谁才是超级英雄 ?
I'm Syndrome! Your nemesis and...
我是辛拉登，你的死对头
Oh, brilliant!
这下好了
All right, try this one on for size, big boy.
现在见识这小玩意的威力
"Kronos?"
克歇诺斯?
Life reading negative. Mr. Incredible terminated.
没有生命踊象 超能先生唱到消沽
This project has completely confiscated my life, darling.
我为这案子投注全副心力
Consumed me as only hero work can. My best work, I must admit.
我只会锅超人特攻降这广做 这是我最好的作品
Simple, elegant, yet bold. You will die.
简章大方、大脆前本 你一定会爱死了
- E, I just... - 1 did Robert's suit,
衣夫人，我只是… 我替鸳伯做了新超能装
and it turned out so beautiful, l had to continue.
我把它做得超炫的 所以就停不下来
It's great to see you, but I have no idea what you're talking about.
很高必见到 不遇我不知道你在说什么
- I just... - Yes, words are useless.
我只是… 没错，光说没有用
Too much of it, darling. Too much!
来吧，大家都光说不
That is why I show you my work.
我要带你去亲眼目睹
That is why you are here.
所以我才把你找来
Edna Mode.
克夫人
And guest.
还有客人
Come. Sit.
遇来，坐吧
- Cream and sugar? - Thanks.
加奶业和糖吗 ? 谢了
- [ started with the baby. - Started?
第一件是裤裤的超能装 第一件?
Darling! I cut it a little roomy for the free movement.
咏，剪裁合身壕合爬动
The fabric is comfortable for sensitive skin,
玛柔的布料不会伤到媚嫩肌刍
and can also withstand a temperature of over 1000 degrees.
它能耐播氏538度的高温
Completely bulletproof.
而且有防弹功能
And machine washable. That's a new feature.
可用洗衣机洗涤，这是新功能
What on earth do you think the baby will be doing?
以禹实裤要做什么呀 ?
Well, I'm sure I don't know, darling. Luck favors the prepared.
我怎入知道 ? 不遇有准备比较好
I didn't know the baby's powers, so I covered the basics.
我不知道他有什么超能力 所以基本功能都有顾到
- Jack-Jack doesn't have any powers. - No?
小傈闪没有超能力 是吗?
Well, he'll look fabulous anyway.
他穿起来还是很可爱
Your boy's suit l designed to withstand enormous friction
小屎的超能装 耐摩探性超强
without heating up or wearing out. A useful feature.
再大的摩探都不会明热或损玉
Your daughter's suit was tricky.
你女儿的超能装就比较坏手
I finally created a sturdy material that will disappear completely as she does.
我终人於找到一种坚固材轿 可以跟著她一起隐形
Your suit can stretch as far as you can, without injuring yourself,
你的超能装的弹性跟你一柑好
and still retain its shape.
马上就能恢复原状
Virtually indestructible...
价国耐穿
..yet it breathes like Egyptian cotton.
而且跟金埃及棉一样透气
As an extra feature, each suit contains a homing device,
每一件超能装都有追跷装置
giving you the precise global location of the wearer at the touch of a button.
只要按一下按鳃 就知道精确的位置
Well, darling? What do you think?
亲爱的，你党得怎术 ?
What do I think? Bob is retired! I'm retired!
我觉得怎样 ? 锡伯趴我都退休了
Our family is underground.
我们全家都销静匿驮
You helped my husband resume secret hero work behind my back?
你背著我 偷偷帮鸳伯重操昔业吗?
Well, l assumed you knew, darling.
我以禹你早就知道了
Why would he keep secrets from you?
他篇什么要孙著人呢 ?
He wouldn't. Didn't. Doesn't.
他从以前到现在都不会蚁著我
Men at Robert's age are often unstable.
他这年纪的男人很搞怪
Prone to weakness.
很容易受到诱惑
- What are you saying? - Do you know where he is?
什么意思 ? 人知道他在哪儿中?
- Of course.
当然知道 人真的知道吗 ?
- Hey, hey. We got a man down! - Come on, let's go.
这儿有人受伤 我们走吧
Are you okay? What happened?
发生什么事 ?
Break surveillance and engage. Over. Continuing sweep...
停止监控，展并攻击
- Insuricare. - Oh, hello. This is Helen Parr.
关心人毒 我是巴荷莉
Bob Parr is my husband. l was wondering if you could give me
巴闻伯的太太 请你把他饭店的电话给我
the number of the hotel he's staying at? The number I have is no good.
他给我的号码打不通
- Mr. Parr no longer works here. - What do you mean?
巴先生不在本公司上班了 什么意思 ?
He's on a business trip. A company retreat.
公司派他去出差开会
My records say he was terminated almost two months ago.
他在雨个月前就被并除了
So, you don't know where he is.
人不知道他在哪儿
Would you like to find out?
人想知道吗 ?
lam such an idiot.
我真是个傻瓜
I let this happen, you know.
我竟然都看不出来
The new sports car, the getting in shape, the blond hair, the lies.
新车、瘦身、梁曼、议言
Yes, he attempts to relive the past.
他只是想重漫蔷切
Now I'm losing him! What'll 1 do? What'll 1 do?
不 ! 我会失去他 我该怎广办呢 ?
What are you talking about?
你在器个什么有动 ?
You are Elastigirl! My God! Pull yourself together.
人是弹力女超人耶 拜旗你振作一吕
What will you do? Is this a question?
你该怎麻办?这膛用周吗 ?
Show him you remember that he is Mr. Incredible,
你要向他证明人记得他是谁
and you will remind him who you are!
也要提醒他你是谁
Well, you know where he is. Go! Confront the problem! Fight! Win!
人知道他在哪儿，快去找他 主动出击，赢得腾利
And call me when you get back, darling. I enjoy our visits.
回来以后再找我 我很喜霓跟你聊天
There's lots of leftovers that you can reheat.
狐了就热剩菜来吃
Make sure Dash does his homework. And both of you, get to bed on time.
记得要盯小飞做功课 时间到了你们就冬冬睡党
I should be back tonight. Late.
我会很晚才回来
You can be in charge that long, can't you?
你能当家作主吧?
Yeah. But why am I in charge again?
行，可是我干桨当家作主 ?
Nothing. Just a little trouble with Daddy.
没事哎，只是和葡和爸有加麻烦
You mean Dad's in trouble, or Dad is the trouble?
你是说爸有麻烦 还是他就是麻烦 ?
I mean either he's in trouble, or he's going to be.
要是他没有麻烦 他的廊烦就大了
What's that? Where'd you get that, Mom?
那是什么 ? 从哪来的?
You made a cool outfit? Hey, are those for us?
那是你做的吐? 要给我们穿的吐?
We all get cool outfits?
我们都有起酷的超能装耶
Dash! You come back here this moment!
小头，给我回来
Hey, Snug. Thanks for getting back.
小史，谢谢你回电
I know this is short notice, but I was hoping that I could...
这是急事，我想请你…
What are these? Look, I'm The Dash!
这是什么 ? 人看，我是赤毛腿
- The Dash likes. - Just a second.
飞毛腿很喜霓 等一下
- Take that off before somebody sees. - You're packing one just like it.
快晚掉，列被人看到了 人自己也带了一件去
- Are you hiding something? - Please. I'm on the phone...
你是不是螨了什么事 ? 我在讲电话
- Dash! - This is yours. It's specially made.
小科 ! 这是你的，很特别哦
- What's going on? - You're not coming! I gotta pack!
这是怎广回事 ? 你们不能跟来，我要打包
What makes you think it's special?
你怎订知道很特别 ?
I don't know. Why'd Mom try to hide it?
不晓得 不然妈干嘛要把它藏起来 ?
Snug, I'm calling in a solid you owe me.
小史，你入我一份人情
- What do you need? - Ajet. What do you got that's fast?
你需要什么 ? 一架喷射机，你有吗 ?
Island approach. India Golf niner-niner checking in.
呼叫小岛 这是IG99疆
VFR on top. Over.
进行目测趟行，请回答
Island tower, this is India Golf niner-niner
呼叫塔台，这是IG99吕
requesting vectors to the initial. Over.
请给我降落座标，请回答
Easy, Helen. Easy. Easy, girl.
荷莉，放轻蕊
You're overreacting. Everything's fine. They're just all getting coffee.
你在竺紧张，不会有事 他们只是…去喝咖啡
At the same time. Yeah.
大家都一起去，没错
You sir, truly are "Mr. Incredible".
你真的是超能先生
I was right to idolize you.
难怪当年我那广棠拜你
l always knew you were tough, but tricking the probe
我知道你很强 你利用一具骨骨
by hiding under the bones of another super? Oh, man!
躲过抬描侦测，真是了不起
I'm still geeking out about it!
我创服得五体投地
And then you had to just go and ruin the ride.
可是你偏偏要让我大失所望
I mean, Mr. Incredible calling for help? "Help me, help me."
超能先生向人求救 ? 救救我 ! 救救我 !
Lame, lame, lame.
避敬了
- All right, who did you contact? - Contact? What are you talking about?
你跟谁联络 ? 联络?你在说什么 ?
lam referring to last night at 2307 hours
昨晚23时07分
while you were snooping around. You sent out a homing signal.
你偷偷摸摸发送了追跳信纺
I didn't know about the homing device.
我根本就不知道这件事
And now a government plane is requesting permission to land here.
有一架政府专机要求降落
- Who did you contact? - didn't send for a plane.
你到底跟谁联络 ? 我没有跟任何人联络
Play the transmission.
播放通话内容
- India golf niner-niner checking in. - Helen!
这是IG99喷，请回答 荷痢 !
So you do know these people.
你果然认识他们
Well, then, I'll send them a little greeting.
那我就要好好数迎他们
- Violet! - It's not my fault.
小依! 不是我的错
Dash ran away, I knew I'd get blamed for it.
是小飞先躲人进来 我就知道你会怪我
That's not true!
才不是
You said, "Something's up with Mom. We have to find out what.
是说要查出妈在搞什么鬼
- ..and it's not my fault! - Hundred percent all-yours idea!
才不是呢
Wait a minute. You left Jack-Jack alone?
慢著，你们于下小保吗?
- Of course we got a sitter. - We got someone, Mom.
我有那广策吗 ? 我当然找了保姆叶
- We wouldn't do that. - Thanks a lot!
我才不会那广不负责任呢 多谢了
All right, well, who'd you get?
人找了谁?
You don't have to worry about one thing.
娩放心啦，巴太太 我超会带小孩
I've got babysitting wired. I've taken courses, learned CPR,
我上遇课，学遇心肺复区本
- excellent marks and certificates. - Kari.
我以优旺的成绩拿到证韦 山莉
I brought Mozart to play while he sleeps
他睡著后我会放英杞特的音乐
because leading experts say Mozart makes babies smarter.
专家说 宰裤凰英札特会爸隐明吕
Kari...
山莉
The beauty is they don't have to listen ‘cause they're asleep!
而且他在睡觉，根本就不用职
I wish my parents played Mozart
我小时候 我爸妈没放黄杞特给我了
because half the time I don't know what anyone's talking about.
所以现在我都匠不懂别人的话
Kari, I really don't feel comfortable with this.
我觉得这不太妥当
I'll pay you for your trouble, but I'd rather call a service.
我要另请高明，的仅照付
There's really no need, Mrs. Parr.
不用啦，巴太太
I can totally handle anything this baby can dish out.
我能照顾你的小实赛
Can't I, little baby? I can handle it.
对不对呀 ? 我会照顾你
Who can handle it?
谁来照顾你呀 ?
India Golf niner-niner transmitting in the blind guard.
IG99号紧急呼叫
Disengage. Repeat, disengage.
请解除飞弹
- Friendlies... - No! Call off the missiles.
这是友机 快解除屎弹
- I'll do anything. - Too late. Fifteen years too late.
我什千都肯做 太晚了，晚了十五年
Friendlies two-zero miles south-southwest of your position.
(推动器)
Vi! Put a force field around the plane.
小倩，快发出防访章
You said not to use our powers.
人不准我用超能力
I know what I said. Listen to what I'm saying now!
我知道，现在贡我的话
Disengage. Repeat, disengage!
请解除飞弹
- Mom? - Violet!
杂? 小依!
Mayday. India Golf niner-niner is buddy-spiked. Abort!
求救，这是友机，请解除飞弹
There are children aboard.
机上有小孩
- There are children aboard! - No!
不 !
- Put a field around us now! - I've never done one that big.
发出防访章保访我们 我没发遇这广大的防访辕
Abort, abort, abort!
请取消攻贡
Brace yourselves!
准备好
- Mom! - Everybody calm down.
妈 ! 大家都冷静下来
I'll tell you what we're not gonna do.
我们一定要冷静
We're not gonna panic, we're not... Look out!
绝对不能车慌，小心 !
- Oh, my God! Who's idea was this? - What are we gonna do?
这是谁的馒主意 ? 我们该怎广办 ?
We're dead! We're dead!
我们死定了 ! 死定了 !
- It blew up! - We survived but we're dead!
飞机被炸成碎片 没被炸死也会被淹死
Stop it!
列吵了
We are not gonna die!
我们不会死
Both of you will get a grip.
你们不冷都下来
Or so help me I will ground you for a month!
我就胃你们禁足一个月
Understand?
明白吗?
We have a confirmed hit. Target was destroyed.
确认击中目标，目标遭到负沽
You'll get over it.
你不会难遇太久的
l seem to recall you prefer to "work alone".
我记得你说你习惯一个人
Release me. Now!
放了我，快点
- Or what? - I'll crush her.
要不然吃? 我就把她捏扁
That sounds a little dark for you. Well, go ahead.
你好狠哦，有有就动手呀
It'll be easy. Like breaking a toothpick.
这就跟捏断牙工一样容易
Show me.
证明给我看
I knew you couldn't do it.
我就知道你狠不下心
Even when you have nothing to lose.
就算你全都豁出去了
You're weak.
你太丑弱了
And I've outgrown you.
我比你强太多了
Those were short-range missiles. Land-based.
那些是短程站弹 从地面发射
That way is our best bet.
我们最好往那儿去
You want to go toward the people that tried to kill us?
你想要自投四网咽 ?
- If it means land, yes. - Do you expect us to swim there?
陆地在那儿 人要我们游过去吐 ?
l expect you to trust me.
我要你们相信我
What a trooper.
好孩子
I'm so proud of you.
我真是以你为药
Thanks, Mom.
谢了，妈
I think your father is in trouble.
我想爸和爸一定有了麻烦
If you haven't noticed, we're not doing so hot either.
也许没看到 我们的麻烦也不小耶
I'm going to look for him.
我要去找他
And that means you're in charge until l get back, Violet.
我回来之前你要当家作主
- What? - You heard her.
什么 ? 你匠到了
Put these on. Your identity is your most valuable possession.
戴上了眼章 你们的身份很裤贵
Protect it.
一定要保护好
And if anything goes wrong, use your powers.
要是有危险就使用超能力
- But you said never to use... - [know what I said!
可是你以前说… 我知道我以前怎广说
Remember the bad guys on those shows you used to watch on Saturday mornings?
记得电视卡通壬 出现的那些壤人吗 ?
Well, these guys are not like those guys.
这些壤人跟那些壤人不同
They won't exercise restraint because you're children.
他们不会因高 你们是小孩放通你们
They will kill you if they get the chance.
他们还到机会就会条了你们
Do not give them that chance.
列计他们还到机会
- Mom? - Vi, I'm counting on you.
杂? 小倩，我都靠你了
- There's... - I'm counting on you. Be strong.
我有话要… 全都靠你了，要坚强
Dash, if anything goes wrong, I want you to run as fast as you can.
小郝，要是有危险 你能跑多快就跑多快
- As fast as l can? - As fast as you can.
多快都行吐 ? 多快都行
Stay hidden. Keep each other safe. I'll be back by morning.
待在这儿，互相照应 我一早就回来
Mom!
杂
Mom, what happened on the plane. I'm sorry.
我在飞机上让人失望了
l wanted to help. When you asked me to... I'm sorry.
我很想帮忙，对不起
It isn't your fault.
不是你的错
It wasn't fair for me to suddenly ask so much of you.
我不该突然对你要求这广多
But things are different now.
但是现在情况不同了
And doubt is a luxury we can't afford anymore, sweetie.
你不能怀疑自己的能力
You have more power than you realize.
你反有强大的能力
Don't think. And don't worry.
别想太多，也别担心
If the time comes, you'll know what to do.
到了时候你就知道该怎广做
He's not weak, you know.
他闪不刁弱
What?
什么 ?
Valuing life is not weakness.
尊重生命不是刁弱
Look, if you're talking about what happened in the containment unit,
如果是在讲刚才的事
l had everything under control.
一切都在我的控制下
And disregarding it is not strength.
枉顾生命闪不算强者
I called his bluff, sweetheart, that's all.
我没被他路住，我赌赢了
I knew he wouldn't have it in him to actually...
我就知道他没种真的下手
Next time you gamble, bet your own life!
下炊你用自己的命去赌
Hey!
哩1 区
Well, not that this isn't fun, but I'm gonna go look around.
不明我要到处看看
What do you think is going on here? You think we're on vacation?
你还是没搞懂吗 ? 我们不是在度假耶
Mom and Dad's lives could be in jeopardy.
和葡妈的生命有危险
Or worse, their marriage.
他们的婚姻也有危机
Their marriage?
婚姻危机 ?
So, the bad guys are trying to wreck Mom and Dad's marriage.
这些壤人想破束和苞妈的婚姻 ?
Forget it. You're so immature.
算了，你太幼和蕉了
- I'm gonna go look around. - Mom said to stay hidden.
我要去到处看看 妈叫我们诅在这儿
I'm not gonna leave the cave.
我不会走出山洞
Cool!
酷鉴了
Roger. We are ready for launch.
收到，汗人备发射
- Vi, Vi! - What did you do?
小依! 你做了什么 ?
ETA two-niner. Over.
预计29分甸和后抵达
TCl clear. Condition yellow. Status norm.
没问题，一切正常
Not responding to IFF.
IFF没有反应
IRCM reads negative.
IRCM没有读数
- Bob. - What?
老公 你说什么 ?
I didn't say anything.
我什么也疙说
Identification, please.
请表明身份
- Hey! Hey, Violet! Come here, look. - What?
小倩，看，它会讲话耶 什么 ?
- It talks!
它会说话耶 什么东西?
There. That one.
那儿，那焦小岛
- "Voice key"? - Voice key incorrect.
语音密码 ?
Wait a second.
等一下
- What do we do? - Run!
我们该怎广办 ? 快跑
- Where are we going? - Away from here!
跑去哪儿 ? 越下越好
Intruder alert.
发现入侵者…
- There isn't much time. - No, there isn't.
时间不多了 没错
In fact, there's no time at all.
你的时间不多了
- Please... - Why are you here?
求求你 你来干六 ?
How can you possibly bring me lower? What more can you take away from me?
你膛想害我吐 ? 你已经千走我的家人
Family survived the crash.
你的家人…没有死
- They're here on the island! - They're alive?
他们到了小岛上 他们膛活著 ?
- Helen? - Hello.
荷莉? 娩好
You must be Mrs...
娩一定是巴太太
- She was helping me to escape. - No.
她来救我出去 才怪
That's what I was doing.
我才是来救你的
Let go of me!
放手
Let go, you lousy, lying, unfaithful creep!
你这满口议言的大料人
How could I betray the perfect woman?
我怎广会背叛我的完美龙人?
- Oh, you're referring to me now? - Where are the kids?
你是指我吗 ? 孩子们呢 ?
- They triggered the alert. - What?
他们触动了警伶 什么 ?
- Security's in the jungle. Get going. - Our kids are in danger?
他们被追进一林，快去吧 我们的孩子有危险?
If you suspected danger, why'd you bring them?
称为什么把他们带来 ?
They stowed away. You're not striking the proper tone.
我没有，是他们偷偷跟来 我不喜霓你的语气
- Think they're supers? - Dash, remember what Mom said.
他们是超人吐 ? 小屎，记得妈说的话
- What? - Stop talking!
什么话 ? 列讲话
- Hold it! Freeze! - Dash, run!
站住 小屎，快跑
- What? - Run!
什么 ? 快跑啊
- They're supers! - Get the boy!
他们是超人 抓住那小匈
Show yourself!
现身吧
But I didn't want you to worry.
我只是不想让你担心
You didn't want me to worry?
你不想让我担心 ?
We're running for our lives through some godforsaken jungle.
现在你甸害我们在王林壬 为了逃避追条疫藉奔命
You keep trying to pick a fight, but I'm just happy you're alive.
随怎广胃，只棣没事就好
I know you're there, Little Miss Disappear.
我知道你在这儿，隐形女孩
You can't hide from me.
姐不了我的
- There you are. - Hey!
还到了 喂!
Don't touch my sister!
列动我老姊
- How are you doing that? - [don't know!
我也不知道
Whatever you do, don't stop!
别停下来
Mom! Dad! Hey!
和爸、妈
Kids.
孩子们
- You're all right.
你们没事
- We were so worried. - [ thought I'd never see you again.
我们担心得要匹 我以贺再也见不到你们
- [love you.
我爱你
Time out!
斩停
What have we here? Matching uniforms?
这是怎样 ? 大家穿制服吗 ?
Oh, no! Elastigirl?
不是吧，弹力女超人 ?
You married Elastigirl?
你要了弹力女超人?
And got busy!
还生了一高小孩
It's a whole family of supers.
一家子的超人
Looks like I've hit the jackpot!
这下我发了
This is just too good!
这真是棒呆了
- The ship's unique design... - There were no fatalities...
飞船的设计独特 没有造成伤亡
Oh, come on! You gotta admit, this is cool.
拜旗，你们得承认这酷蜂了
Just like a movie! The robot will emerge dramatically,
就像志影演的一样 机器人会跑出来大搞破玉
do some damage. Throngs of screaming people!
把训老百姓车静尖只
And just when all hope is lost, Syndrome will save the day!
就当一切都绝望的时候 辛拉司就来抒救世界
I'll be a bigger hero than you ever were!
我会成贺比你更伟大的英雄
You mean you killed off real heroes so that you could pretend to be one?
你般死真正的英雄 好让你当冒牌货?
I'm real. Real enough to defeat you!
我不是冒牌货，我打败了你
And I did it without your precious gifts, your oh-so-special powers.
而且我不像你撞有超人能力
I'll give them heroics.
超能力有什么了不起?
I'll give them the most spectacular heroics anyone's ever seen!
我才会是史上最了不起的英雄
And when I'm old and I've had my fun, I'll sell my inventions
等我老了玩级了 就会把我的发明廉价大拍喜
so that everyone can be superheroes. Everyone can be super.
每个人都能成为超级英雄 每个人都有超能力
And when everyone's super...
当人人都是超级英雄
..No one will be.
世上就没有英雄了
It's overwhelming the tanks.
连坦克车都揽不住它
I'm sorry.
对不起
This is my fault. I've been a lousy father.
都是我的错 我不是个好和苑区
Blind to what I have. So obsessed with being undervalued
我不懂得珍惜我所所有的 只想著自己不被重视
- that undervalued all of you. - Dad?
我完全部负了你们 邓
Don't interrupt.
列插噶
So caught up in the past that I...
我一直忘不辽去的荣光
You are my greatest adventure. And I almost missed it.
其实你们才是我最大的颈侈 我差点就失去你们
I swear, I'm gonna get us out of this safely if I...
我发专我会把你们救出去
Well, l think Dad has made some excellent progress today
老苞今天的心理治疗很有进展
but I think it's time we wind down now.
不通也该结束了吧
We need to get back to the mainland.
我们得超回城市
I saw an aircraft hangar on my way in. Straight ahead.
我看到有一座停机棚 麻该就在前面
Where are all the guards?
警卫呢 ?
Go, go!
快去，快去
Hey, every time they run, you take a shot.
他们一跑就会换一检
This is the right hangar, but I don't see any jets.
就是这儿没错 可是我没看到飞机
- Ajet's not fast enough. - What's faster than a jet?
科机不级快 有什么更快的?
How about a rocket?
火箭如何?
- Great! I can't fly a rocket. - You don't have to.
太好了，我不会并火箭 你不必开火笠
Use the coordinates from the last launch.
只要用上一炎的座标就行
Wait. l bet Syndrome's changed the password by now.
等等，辛拉登一定换了密码
- How do I get into the computer? - Say please.
我要怎麻进入电脑 ? 说声拜旗
- Honey? - What?
老婆 ? 干乌?
- Where is my supersuit?
我的超能装呢 ? 你说什么 ?
Where is my supersuit?
我的超能装在哪里?
- [ put it away. - Where?
我收起来了 收到哪里 ?
Why do you need to know?
你干六要知道 ?
I need it!
我需要它
Don't you think about running off to doing no derrin'-do.
我不准你跑去有还英雄
We've been planning this dinner for two months!
二个月前我就计另好这上顿晚餐
Tell me where my suit is, woman! We are talking about the greater good.
我要去救人，这是各了大党
"Greater good"? 1 am your wife!
大什么爱，我是你老赣耶
I'm the greatest good you are ever gonna get!
我才是你一生中最大的爱
Run!
快跑啊
- The supers have returned! - ls that Fironic?
超人特攻队回来了 那是火球人吐?
- Fironic? - No, Fironic has a different outfit.
火球人? 不是啦，他的打扮不一样
No, no, I'm a new superhero! I'm Syndrome!
我是辛拉登
All right, stand back.
好了，退和后
Someone needs to teach this hunk of metal a few manners.
我要好好教训这扒破铜烟钱
- Are we there yet? - We get there when we get there.
到了没有 ? 到了你就会知道
How you doing, honey?
老娑，逮好吧 ?
Do I have to answer?
我一定要回答吗 ?
Kids, strap yourselves down like I told you.
孩子们，把安全带索好
Here we go, honey.
我们到了
Ready, Violet? Ready?
准备好了吗 ?
Now!
现在 !
This is gonna be rough.
这会很颠繁哦
Robot's in the financial district. Which exit?
机咽人在金融区 哪个交流道下?
- Traction Avenue. - That'll take me downtown.
大千路 那是到市区
- 1 take Seventh, don't I? - Don't take Seventh!
我要走七街 不行
- Great, we missed it. - Ask how to get there, I told you.
错通了 你要我指路，我说了
- Traction. - That'll take me downtown.
在大千路下 那会并到市区
Get in the right lane! Signal!
换到右线，打媒
- Not Traction! - You're gonna miss it!
不对啦 你就快错 了
Is everybody okay back there?
你们还好吧 ?
- Super-duper, Dad! - Let's do that again.
再玩一次
Wait here and stay hidden. I'm going in.
你留在这儿，我去对付它
While what? l watch helplessly from the sidelines?
这是怎样 ? 我只能乱助地在劣焉看 ?
- [don't think so. - I'm asking you to wait with the kids.
想都列想 我要你留在孩子身遵
And I'm telling you not a chance. You're my husband.
我说想都列想，你是我老公
I'm with you for better or worse.
不管怎样都要互相扶持
l have to do this alone.
我必须一个人去
- What is this to you? Playtime? - No.
你这是在玩闭戏吐 ? 不是
- So you can be Mr. Incredible? - No!
你是想膛英雄吗 ?
- Then what? - I'm not...
那是怎样 ? 我不…
- Not what? - I'm not strong enough.
我不久强
- This will make you stronger? - Yes. No!
你一个人去就金强中 ? 对，不是
That's what this is? A workout?
你是想去送死唉 ?
I can't lose you again!
我不能再失去你
I can't. Not again.
我不能失去你
I'm not... strong enough.
我不金坚强
If we work together, you won't have to be.
我们一起去你就不会失去我
I don't know what'll happen.
我不知道会发生什么事
We're superheroes. What can happen?
我们是超级英雄 会发生什么事 ?
Vi! Dash! No!
小傅、小丧，不!
Violet?
小倩 ?
- Dad! - Go, go!
和爸! 快走啊
- I'm okay, Mom. Really. - Stay here, okay?
我没事，真的 留在这儿
Frozone!
酷冰使
Yeah!
好耶
Bob!
锡伯
Hey!
喂!
Syndrome's remote!
辛拉司的选控器
The remote controls the robot!
狗控器能用来控制机器人
- Throw it, throw it! - Go long!
和爸，丢遇来 哆速一点
Got it!
我接到了
Honey, take out its guns!
把它的火雹打掉
Gotcha!
没问题
Mom, I've got it! I've got the remote!
我拿到道控器了
A remote? A remote that controls what?
记控器 ? 控制什么的适控器 ?
The robot?
机器人?
It's coming back!
它回来了
- That wasn't right. - Give me that!
按错了 给我啦
We can't stop it. The only thing hard enough to penetrate it is...
阻止不了它 它唯一的刘星就是…
. itself.
它自己
It's getting closer!
它过来了
- It doesn't work! - Kids!
没有用 孩子们 !
It's not doing anything.
一点用都没有
- Try to buy us some time. - Try the one next to it.
替我各取时间 等等，试试劣尊的按鳃
Honey!
老婆 !
Wait a minute. Press that button again!
这就对了，再按一次
- No, the other one! The first one! - First button! Got it!
另一个，第一个按鳃 第一个，收到
- It's getting closer! - Look out!
它过来了 小心了
- Get out of here! - We're not going anywhere.
找地方租起来 我们才不走
- Press the button! - Not yet!
快按呀 还不行
- Hang on! - What are you waiting for?
等一下 你还在等什么 ?
Acloser target! You got one shot!
等它靠近一点，只有一次机会
Everybody duck!
大家快躲开
Hey, Zone.
酷哥
No!
不 !
Did you see that? That's the way to do it.
你看到吗 ? 这样才对
- That's old school. - Yeah. No school like the old school.
这些老超人真行 是啊，昔还是老的头
- Just like old times.
就跟以前一样 吐以前一样
Yeah. Hurt then too.
也跟以前一样痛
We've frozen all of Syndrome's assets.
我们闵结了辛拉有悚的剖产
If he even sneezes, we'll be there with a hanky and a pair of handcuffs.
只要他敢轻举妄动 我们就会还到他
The people of this country are indebted to you.
国家欠你们一份人情
Can we come out of hiding?
我们不必隐姓埋名了吐?
Let the politicians figure that out.
这要让政客去决定
I've been asked to assure you we'll take care of everything else.
不明我们一定会好好照顾你们
You did good, Bob.
你做得很好
Hi, this is Kari.
这是凯莉
! have a question about Jack-Jack...
小傈有黑问题
Come on. We're in a limo.
这是礼车，给我安份一点
Hey, you're wearing your hair back?
你把头权手到和后面了
- Yeah, I just... yeah. - It looks good.
是啊，我想…对啊 这样很好看
- Thanks, Dad. - That was cool when you threw that car!
谢了 你委那辆车超栈的
Not as cool as you running on water.
你在水上跑也酷鉴了
That was sweet when you snagged that bad guy with your arm
你伸手把那款蛋 打赤出去撞到另一个像伙
and whiplashed him into the other guy. Sweet!
那一招超装的
- I'm trying to listen to messages. - Mrs. Parr, it's me.
我正在贩留言 巴太太，是我
Jack-Jack is fine, but weird things are happening.
小休没事 不明发生了一些怪事
Jack-Jack's still fine, but I'm getting really weirded out!
小傈很好，不遇我一点都不好
When are you coming back?
你修时才会回来 ?
..aced those guys that tried to kill us!
我们把壤蛋打得落花流水
That was the best vacation ever! I love our family.
我爱我的家人
I'm not fine, Mrs. Parr!
我糟糕延顶了
Put that down! Stop it! You need to call me.
快点放下来，住手 请你超快打电话给我
! need help, Mrs...
我需要帮忙
Bob, listen to this.
你职职
I'm gonna calf the police...
我要报鳌了
Hi, this is Kari.
这是凯莉
Sorry for freaking out, but your baby has special needs.
我太大敬小怪了 不遇的实实很特别
Thanks for sending a replacement.
谢谢你找专业保姆来帮忙
I didn't call a replacement.
我汽有找保姆呀
The baby is sleeping.
赛裤睡著了
You took away my future.
你们夺走我的未来
I'm simply returning the favor. Don't worry, I'll be a good mentor.
我只是想报一稍之做 我会好好照顾他
Supportive, encouraging. Everything you weren't.
我会支持他鼓励他 不像你那广扰情
And in time, who knows, he might make a good sidekick.
也许有一天 他可以当我的小跟班
He's getting away, Bob! We have to do something.
他逃走了，快想办法
What's happening?
发生什么事 ?
- Stop him! Throw something! - [might hit Jack-Jack.
快丢东西阻止他 不行，我会琉到小人钦
Throw me.
把我和上去
Bob, throw me!
快把我雪上去
No!
不 !
This isn't the end of it! I will get your son, eventually.
我不会放通你们 名有一天我会报优雪恨
I'll get your son!
我会报做的
Oh, no.
惨了
Look at Mommy, honey. Don't look down. Mommy's got you.
看著妈味，别往下看 妈味抱住你了
Everything is all right.
一切都不会有事
That's my girl.
好孩子
Does this mean we have to move again?
我们又得搬家吗 ?
Oh, man.
哇塞
Do we have to have cheerleaders at the track meet?
田径比赛也有啦啦队 ?
- What is that all about? - lalways thought it was more...
这会不会太扯了? 我老是觉得…
- Hey.
螺
- You're Violet, right? - That's me.
你是小倩，对吧 ?
- See you, Vi. - You look different.
回头见 人看起来不太一样
l feel different. Is different okay?
我感觉也不一样 不一样好吗 ?
Different is great.
不一样…不一样很好
- Yeah? - Do you think maybe...
什么 ?
l like movies. I'll buy the popcorn. Okay?
我喜欢看电影，爆米花我买
A movie. There you go. Yeah.
看电影，好哇
- Wait, so Friday? - Friday.
等等，就约礼拜五唆 礼拜五见
- Go, Dash, go. - Run!
小屎，加油，快跑 跑快一点
Come on, run! Pick up the pace.
加油，跑快一点
Run!
加油
Pull back, pull back!
慢点，慢哑
Pace it. Slow down just a little bit.
列跑那庆快，跑慢一点
- Make it close! - Second.
不要赢太多 得亚军就行了
Close second, yeah!
差距很近的亚军
That's my boy!
好孩子
Dash, I'm so proud of you.
小条 ? 我真是以你为蓉
I didn't know what the heck you wanted me to do.
我都不知道你要我怎样
Behold the Underminer!
我万地狼魔王是也
lam always beneath you,
我一直都在你们底下
but nothing is beneath me!
我可是比上不足，比下有狂
l hereby declare war on peace and happiness!
我要向和平与快乐宣战
Soon all will tremble before me!
你们很快会臣服在我的脚下